<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CoreUI for React.js Changelog on CoreUI</title>
    <link>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/react/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CoreUI for React.js Changelog on CoreUI</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/react/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI for React v5.0.0-rc.3</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/react/v5.0.0-rc.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/react/v5.0.0-rc.3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re excited to announce the release of CoreUI for React v5.0.0-rc.3, available as of March 22, 2024. This latest version introduces enhancements that aim to refine the usability and aesthetic flexibility of our React components. With a focus on improving the integration and customization capabilities for developers, we continue to evolve the CoreUI library to meet the growing demands of modern web development.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI for React v5.0.0-rc.2</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/react/v5.0.0-rc.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/react/v5.0.0-rc.2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re pleased to announce CoreUI for React v5.0.0-rc.2, a substantial update that brings improvements to component styling, ensuring text readability across different themes and modes, and a sweeping update of dependencies to enhance the performance and compatibility of your projects. Released on March 7, 2024, this version underscores our dedication to providing developers with a robust, efficient, and adaptable environment for building React applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI for React v5.0.0-rc.1</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/react/v5.0.0-rc.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 18:29:11 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/react/v5.0.0-rc.1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our latest release, version 5.0.0-rc.1, introduces significant improvements and updates aimed at enhancing both the developer and user experience. We&amp;rsquo;ve made advancements in handling text directions, ensuring a more intuitive and inclusive interface for users worldwide. This version also sees a comprehensive update to key dependencies, enhancing framework performance and compatibility. Our commitment to maintaining a robust, secure, and efficient development environment is reflected in these updates, keeping our framework aligned with the latest industry standards.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
