<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>changelog on CoreUI</title>
    <link>https://coreui.io/categories/changelog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in changelog on CoreUI</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 12:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://coreui.io/categories/changelog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI for React v5.0.0-rc.2</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/react/v5.0.0-rc.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/react/v5.0.0-rc.2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re pleased to announce CoreUI for React v5.0.0-rc.2, a substantial update that brings improvements to component styling, ensuring text readability across different themes and modes, and a sweeping update of dependencies to enhance the performance and compatibility of your projects. Released on March 7, 2024, this version underscores our dedication to providing developers with a robust, efficient, and adaptable environment for building React applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI PRO for React v5.0.0-rc.2</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/react-pro/v5.0.0-rc.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/react-pro/v5.0.0-rc.2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re thrilled to unveil CoreUI PRO for React v5.0.0-rc.2, bringing forth innovative features and crucial refinements that significantly elevate the development experience. Released on March 7, 2024, this version introduces enhanced capabilities and updates designed to streamline project development with CoreUI and React.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI Free Bootstrap Admin Template v5.0.0-rc.1</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/coreui-free-bootstrap-admin-template/v5.0.0-rc.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 18:29:11 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/coreui-free-bootstrap-admin-template/v5.0.0-rc.1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are excited to announce the release of CoreUI Free Bootstrap Admin Template v5.0.0-rc.1, a significant update that brings enhancements to the responsiveness, style, and overall layout of the template. This release, dated March 4, 2024, marks an important step in our commitment to providing high-quality, user-friendly administrative templates built on the latest technologies.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI PRO v5.0.0-rc.2</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/coreui-pro/v5.0.0-rc.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 18:29:11 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/coreui-pro/v5.0.0-rc.2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re excited to announce the release of version 5.0.0-rc.2, available as of February 29, 2024. This update marks a significant milestone, introducing a range of changes and improvements. A new Bootstrap theme enhances customization options and modernizes project aesthetics. The update to Bootstrap 5.3.3 brings new functionalities and fixes. We&amp;rsquo;ve also significantly bolstered support for Right-to-Left (RTL) text direction, aiding the development of applications for international markets. Dependency updates, including @babel/core, eslint, and sass, have been made to ensure better performance and security for applications. These changes reflect our commitment to providing developers with flexible, up-to-date tools that adhere to the latest standards and practices in software development.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI v5.0.0-rc.2</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/coreui/v5.0.0-rc.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 18:29:11 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/coreui/v5.0.0-rc.2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re excited to announce the release of version 5.0.0-rc.2, available as of February 29, 2024. This update marks a significant milestone, introducing a range of changes and improvements. A new Bootstrap theme enhances customization options and modernizes project aesthetics. The update to Bootstrap 5.3.3 brings new functionalities and fixes. We&amp;rsquo;ve also significantly bolstered support for Right-to-Left (RTL) text direction, aiding the development of applications for international markets. Dependency updates, including @babel/core, eslint, and sass, have been made to ensure better performance and security for applications. These changes reflect our commitment to providing developers with flexible, up-to-date tools that adhere to the latest standards and practices in software development.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI for React v5.0.0-rc.1</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/react/v5.0.0-rc.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 18:29:11 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/react/v5.0.0-rc.1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our latest release, version 5.0.0-rc.1, introduces significant improvements and updates aimed at enhancing both the developer and user experience. We&amp;rsquo;ve made advancements in handling text directions, ensuring a more intuitive and inclusive interface for users worldwide. This version also sees a comprehensive update to key dependencies, enhancing framework performance and compatibility. Our commitment to maintaining a robust, secure, and efficient development environment is reflected in these updates, keeping our framework aligned with the latest industry standards.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI v5.0.0-rc.1</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/coreui/v5.0.0-rc.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 18:29:11 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/coreui/v5.0.0-rc.1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In our latest release, version 5.0.0-rc.1, we&amp;rsquo;ve taken significant steps to improve the handling of both Left-to-Right (LTR) and Right-to-Left (RTL) text directions, ensuring a more intuitive and inclusive experience for users worldwide. We are excited to share that we&amp;rsquo;ve updated key dependencies to enhance our framework&amp;rsquo;s performance and compatibility. These updates are part of our ongoing commitment to provide a robust, secure, and efficient development environment, aligning with the latest industry standards and ensuring our framework remains at the forefront of technology.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI Free Bootstrap Admin Template v5.0.0-rc.0</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/coreui-free-bootstrap-admin-template/v5.0.0-rc.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:29:11 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/coreui-free-bootstrap-admin-template/v5.0.0-rc.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the transition to version 5.0.0-rc.0, we&amp;rsquo;ve focused on enhancing the responsiveness, layout, and styling of our project to deliver a more seamless and visually appealing user experience. These refinements are part of our continuous effort to improve project usability across various devices and screen sizes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI v5.0.0-rc.0</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/coreui/v5.0.0-rc.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:29:11 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/coreui/v5.0.0-rc.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the latest update, we focused on refining both the functionality and the dependencies of our project to ensure an optimal development and user experience. Key highlights include a visual enhancement in the user interface, specifically within the sidebar, where the active icon color has been modified to improve visibility and navigation for users. Additionally, we&amp;rsquo;ve made improvements to the syntax, aiming for better code readability and maintainability.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI v5.0.0-beta.2</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/coreui/v5.0.0-beta.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 18:29:11 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/coreui/v5.0.0-beta.2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In our latest update, we&amp;rsquo;ve focused on refining our project&amp;rsquo;s responsive design and ensuring our dependencies are up to date with the latest standards for improved functionality and performance. By adjusting key variables and upgrading essential tools, we aim to provide a seamless development experience and an optimized end-user interface. Here&amp;rsquo;s a summary of the changes made:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI v5.0.0-beta.1</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/coreui/v5.0.0-beta.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 18:29:11 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/coreui/v5.0.0-beta.1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the latest update, we&amp;rsquo;ve enhanced sidebar functionality and addressed specific styling issues to improve the user interface and experience. This includes making &lt;code&gt;.sidebar-overlaid&lt;/code&gt; hidden by default to streamline appearance, forcefully hiding the sidebar in narrow mode with &lt;code&gt;!important&lt;/code&gt;, adjusting padding values for better usability in compact and narrow modes, and updating the z-index for &lt;code&gt;.sidebar-overlaid&lt;/code&gt; to ensure proper layering. Our refinements focus on ensuring consistent behavior and a more intuitive navigation layout.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
