<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>react on CoreUI</title>
    <link>https://coreui.io/tags/react/</link>
    <description>Recent content in react on CoreUI</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 12:25:49 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://coreui.io/tags/react/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to migrate CoreUI React Templates to Vite</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-migrate-coreui-react-template-to-vite/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-migrate-coreui-react-template-to-vite/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After carefully considering and evaluating our build and development tools in version 5 of our React.js admin templates, we have decided to migrate from Create React App (CRA) to Vite. This decision was driven by several key factors that align with our goals for a more efficient and modern development experience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI PRO Next.js Admin Template v5.0.0-rc.1</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/coreui-pro-next-js-admin-template/v2.0.0-rc.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/coreui-pro-next-js-admin-template/v2.0.0-rc.1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re excited to announce the release of &lt;a href=&#34;https://coreui.io/product/next-js-dashboard-template/&#34;&gt;CoreUI PRO Next.js Admin Template&lt;/a&gt;] v5.0.0-rc.1 on March 23, 2024. This update enhances the template&amp;rsquo;s functionality and compatibility, incorporating fixes and a series of dependency updates to ensure a smooth development experience with the latest web technologies.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI Free React.js Admin Template v5.0.0-rc.1 (CRA)</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/coreui-free-react-admin-template-cra/v5.0.0-rc.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/coreui-free-react-admin-template-cra/v5.0.0-rc.1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are excited to introduce the CoreUI &lt;a href=&#34;https://coreui.io/product/free-react-admin-template/&#34;&gt;Free React.js Admin Template&lt;/a&gt; v5.0.0-rc.1, released on March 22, 2024. This latest version marks a significant milestone in our journey to provide a seamless and modern admin template experience for React developers. With a focus on enhancing functionality, design, and developer experience, v5.0.0-rc.1 brings forth a series of feature upgrades, refactorings, and dependency updates.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI Free React.js Admin Template v5.0.0-rc.1 (Vite)</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/coreui-free-react-admin-template/v5.0.0-rc.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/coreui-free-react-admin-template/v5.0.0-rc.1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re delighted to announce the release of CoreUI &lt;a href=&#34;https://coreui.io/product/free-react-admin-template/&#34;&gt;Free React.js Admin Template&lt;/a&gt; v5.0.0-rc.1 on March 22, 2024. This update signifies a pivotal advancement in our effort to provide the most efficient, modern, and developer-friendly admin template. Focused on enhancing performance, usability, and developer experience, this release incorporates significant feature upgrades, refactorings, and dependency updates.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI PRO React.js Admin Template v5.0.0-rc.1 (CRA)</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/coreui-pro-react-admin-template-cra/v5.0.0-rc.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/coreui-pro-react-admin-template-cra/v5.0.0-rc.1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are pleased to announce the release of &lt;a href=&#34;(/product/react-dashboard-template/)&#34;&gt;CoreUI PRO React.js Admin Template&lt;/a&gt; v5.0.0-rc.1 (CRA) on March 22, 2024. This update brings a wealth of improvements and upgrades, ensuring that developers have access to the most advanced tools and features for building dynamic and responsive admin interfaces.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI PRO React.js Admin Template v5.0.0-rc.1 (Vite)</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/coreui-pro-react-admin-template/v5.0.0-rc.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/coreui-pro-react-admin-template/v5.0.0-rc.1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re excited to unveil the CoreUI PRO React.js Admin Template v5.0.0-rc.1, released on March 22, 2024. This version represents a significant leap forward, embracing the latest web development standards and technologies to provide an enhanced toolkit for building high-quality, responsive admin panels and dashboards.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI for React v5.0.0-rc.3</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/react/v5.0.0-rc.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/react/v5.0.0-rc.3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re excited to announce the release of CoreUI for React v5.0.0-rc.3, available as of March 22, 2024. This latest version introduces enhancements that aim to refine the usability and aesthetic flexibility of our React components. With a focus on improving the integration and customization capabilities for developers, we continue to evolve the CoreUI library to meet the growing demands of modern web development.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI PRO for React v5.0.0-rc.3</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/react-pro/v5.0.0-rc.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/react-pro/v5.0.0-rc.3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are thrilled to announce the latest update, CoreUI PRO for React v5.0.0-rc.3, released on March 22, 2024. This version introduces a series of refinements aimed at enhancing component flexibility, design, and accessibility, alongside crucial dependency updates that ensure your projects leverage the most current web development practices.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI for React v5.0.0-rc.2</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/react/v5.0.0-rc.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/react/v5.0.0-rc.2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re pleased to announce CoreUI for React v5.0.0-rc.2, a substantial update that brings improvements to component styling, ensuring text readability across different themes and modes, and a sweeping update of dependencies to enhance the performance and compatibility of your projects. Released on March 7, 2024, this version underscores our dedication to providing developers with a robust, efficient, and adaptable environment for building React applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI PRO for React v5.0.0-rc.2</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/react-pro/v5.0.0-rc.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/react-pro/v5.0.0-rc.2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re thrilled to unveil CoreUI PRO for React v5.0.0-rc.2, bringing forth innovative features and crucial refinements that significantly elevate the development experience. Released on March 7, 2024, this version introduces enhanced capabilities and updates designed to streamline project development with CoreUI and React.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Inline Styles in React.js: Enhancing Your Components with Style</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-use-inline-styles-in-react/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-use-inline-styles-in-react/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Are you looking to refine your React.js components with a dash of styling, but find yourself tangled in a web of CSS files? Fear not! Inline styles in React can be a powerful tool for developers to directly insert styling properties into their components. Here, we delve into the art of using react inline style, answering critical questions and unveiling the best practices to maximize the potential of your React.js applications. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re painting your first component or tweaking an existing masterpiece, this guide will illuminate the path to impeccable styling within your React projects.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding and Resolving the “Objects Are Not Valid as a React Child” Error in React Development</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-fix-objects-are-not-valid-as-a-react-child/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-fix-objects-are-not-valid-as-a-react-child/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;React has revolutionized the way developers build user interfaces, standing out for its modular approach through components and state management. As with any robust technology, developers, from beginners to veterans, encounter their share of error messages. One that often crops up is the &lt;code&gt;Objects Are Not Valid as a React Child&lt;/code&gt; error. In this comprehensive article, we&amp;rsquo;ll dissect the causes of this error and provide actionable solutions for overcoming it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI for React v5.0.0-rc.1</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/react/v5.0.0-rc.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 18:29:11 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/changelog/coreui/react/v5.0.0-rc.1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our latest release, version 5.0.0-rc.1, introduces significant improvements and updates aimed at enhancing both the developer and user experience. We&amp;rsquo;ve made advancements in handling text directions, ensuring a more intuitive and inclusive interface for users worldwide. This version also sees a comprehensive update to key dependencies, enhancing framework performance and compatibility. Our commitment to maintaining a robust, secure, and efficient development environment is reflected in these updates, keeping our framework aligned with the latest industry standards.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UI Component Libraries: Use or not to use [them] with epic fails and more...</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/ui-component-libraries-use-or-not-to-use-them-with-epic-fails-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/ui-component-libraries-use-or-not-to-use-them-with-epic-fails-and-more/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced world of web and mobile application development, time is of the essence. As such, developers are always looking for ways to speed up their development cycles while maintaining the quality of their applications. One way to do this is by using UI component libraries.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A UI component library is a collection of pre-built user interface elements that can be easily integrated into your application.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to use Bootstrap 5 in React.js - an original tutorial with (not original) examples</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/bootstrap-react-tutorial-with-examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/bootstrap-react-tutorial-with-examples/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bootstrap is a holy Grail for most of us - it&amp;rsquo;s the most popular HTML, CSS and most of all JS library in the world. And as a Christmas miracle—Bootstrap v5.3.0-alpha1 has arrived during the holiday break, so&amp;hellip; let&amp;rsquo;s dig inside and check how to use bootstrap in React.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
