<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on CoreUI</title>
    <link>https://coreui.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on CoreUI</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://coreui.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What is Double Question Mark in JavaScript?</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/what-is-double-question-mark-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/what-is-double-question-mark-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;JavaScript is a dynamic programming language rich in features that empower developers to craft interactive and efficient web applications. Among its plethora of tools and operators, the double question mark, or as it&amp;rsquo;s formally known, the Nullish Coalescing Operator (&lt;code&gt;??&lt;/code&gt;), stands out for its utility and simplicity. This operator, introduced in ECMAScript 2020, is a game-changer for handling variables that might need to be initialized. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive into this operator&amp;rsquo;s what, why, and how to understand its significance and application.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to declare the optional function parameters in JavaScript?</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-declare-the-optional-functions-parameters-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 17:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-declare-the-optional-functions-parameters-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;JavaScript is a versatile language that offers various methods to enhance the flexibility and adaptability of your code, especially when dealing with function parameters. Optional parameters in functions make your functions more flexible and easier to work with, allowing you to specify arguments that may or may not be passed when the function is called. In this article, we will delve into how you can declare optional function parameters in JavaScript, making your journey into web development smoother and more efficient.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Merge Objects in JavaScript</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-merge-objects-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-merge-objects-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When manipulating data in JavaScript, one of the most common challenges developers face is merging objects. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re looking to combine properties or need to weave together complex nested structures intricately, JavaScript offers a variety of methods to achieve your objectives. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll dive into five effective ways to merge two objects in JavaScript, covering both shallow and deep merging techniques. Let&amp;rsquo;s enhance your coding toolkit with these practical solutions.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to round a number to two decimal places in JavaScript</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-round-a-number-to-two-decimal-places-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-round-a-number-to-two-decimal-places-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the ever-evolving landscape of web development, mastering JavaScript nuances can significantly enhance your applications&amp;rsquo; functionality and user experience. A joint yet critical operation in numerous computing scenarios is to round numbers to a specific number of decimal places. Among these, rounding to two decimal places is particularly relevant across financial calculations, statistical reporting, and data presentation for its balance between precision and readability. This comprehensive guide will walk you through the intricacies of rounding numbers to two decimal places in JavaScript, ensuring you confidently apply this operation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to check if a string is a number in JavaScript</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-check-if-string-is-number-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-check-if-string-is-number-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the realm of web development, the versatility and power of JavaScript stand unchallenged. It is pivotal in adding interactivity to websites, working with data, and creating complex web applications. A common hurdle developers often stumble upon is determining whether a given piece of text—more formally, a string—represents a number. This validation is crucial for data processing, form submissions, and other scenarios where numeric input is expected. This comprehensive article explores the methods and best practices for checking if a string is a number in JavaScript, ensuring your code is robust, reliable, and ready for real-world usage.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to check if an array is empty in JavaScript?</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-check-if-an-array-is-empty-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-check-if-an-array-is-empty-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the ever-evolving world of web development, JavaScript stands as a cornerstone, powering dynamic and interactive elements across countless websites and applications. Among its many tasks, one seemingly straightforward yet pivotal operation is determining whether an array is empty. This operation is crucial in various scenarios, such as enabling or disabling buttons based on user input or ensuring data integrity before processing. In this article, part of the &amp;ldquo;how to&amp;rdquo; series, we delve into the intricacies of checking for empty arrays in JavaScript. This guide promises to enlighten those new to the programming world and provide valuable insights for seasoned developers.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering JavaScript List Comprehension: The Ultimate Guide</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/javascript-list-comprehension/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/javascript-list-comprehension/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;JavaScript list comprehension may not have a dedicated syntax like Python or Perl, but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean it&amp;rsquo;s any less powerful. In a realm dominated by dynamic data and the need for efficient operations on arrays, understanding how to perform list comprehension in JavaScript is indispensable for developers. This comprehensive guide will walk you through the practical nuances of array manipulation using JavaScript, offering vivid examples to transform you into a master of efficient list handling.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Inline Styles in React.js: Enhancing Your Components with Style</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-use-inline-styles-in-react/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-use-inline-styles-in-react/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Are you looking to refine your React.js components with a dash of styling, but find yourself tangled in a web of CSS files? Fear not! Inline styles in React can be a powerful tool for developers to directly insert styling properties into their components. Here, we delve into the art of using react inline style, answering critical questions and unveiling the best practices to maximize the potential of your React.js applications. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re painting your first component or tweaking an existing masterpiece, this guide will illuminate the path to impeccable styling within your React projects.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding and Resolving the “Objects Are Not Valid as a React Child” Error in React Development</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-fix-objects-are-not-valid-as-a-react-child/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-fix-objects-are-not-valid-as-a-react-child/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;React has revolutionized the way developers build user interfaces, standing out for its modular approach through components and state management. As with any robust technology, developers, from beginners to veterans, encounter their share of error messages. One that often crops up is the &lt;code&gt;Objects Are Not Valid as a React Child&lt;/code&gt; error. In this comprehensive article, we&amp;rsquo;ll dissect the causes of this error and provide actionable solutions for overcoming it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to get the last element in an array in JavaScript</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-get-the-last-element-in-an-array-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-get-the-last-element-in-an-array-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;JavaScript arrays are fundamental structures in any developer&amp;rsquo;s arsenal, designed to store multiple values in a single, easy-to-manage variable. But no matter how proficient you are in JavaScript, there are always new tricks to learn and old ones to be reminded of. One such handy trick is retrieving the last element of an array—an operation that might seem straightforward but comes with nuances worth understanding. In this deep dive into JavaScript arrays, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore multiple ways to get to that elusive last item and offer insights into which method suits your coding needs best.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to compare dates with JavaScript</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-compare-dates-with-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-compare-dates-with-javascript/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As the digital world intertwines more deeply with our lives, understanding the intricacies of web development becomes increasingly relevant. JavaScript stands at the forefront of this realm, with its ability to enrich user experiences. Among its many capabilities, the power to compare dates in JavaScript is a particularly useful skill that enables developers to deal with schedules, events, and time-based data more effectively.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to disable a button in JavaScript</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-disable-a-button-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-disable-a-button-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the intricate dance of web development, JavaScript plays a crucial role in choreographing dynamic interactions. One such interaction is the ability to enable or disable buttons on a web page. Disabling a button may seem straightforward, but it serves as a critical user experience (UX) feature, ensuring users only take actions when the time is right. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the art of disabling a button in JavaScript, guiding you through a variety of methods with intuitive code examples—and don&amp;rsquo;t worry; we&amp;rsquo;ll keep the jargon in check.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to check if a key exists in JavaScript object?</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-check-if-a-key-exists-in-javascript-object/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-check-if-a-key-exists-in-javascript-object/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the intricate world of JavaScript, a common task for developers is determining whether a specific key exists within an object. It&amp;rsquo;s an elementary, yet crucial skill that can significantly affect the flow and reliability of your code. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll unearth the various methods to perform this check, unravel their nuances, and understand how to apply them, even in complex nested structures. By the end of this article, you&amp;rsquo;ll be equipped with the expertise to write robust and error-free JavaScript applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to remove elements from a JavaScript Array</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-remove-element-from-javascript-array/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-remove-element-from-javascript-array/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Have you ever faced the challenge of removing a specific item from an array in JavaScript and found yourself puzzled with various methods and unsure which one to use? Arrays are fundamental structures in programming that store collections of data. However, understanding how to manipulate them efficiently, especially when it comes to removing elements, is crucial for a streamlined code. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;re going to demystify the process of removing elements from JavaScript arrays. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a budding programmer or a seasoned developer looking to brush up on your skills, this guide is designed to provide you with everything you need to handle array modifications with confidence.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Migrate from create-react-app to Vite?</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-migrate-create-react-app-to-vite/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-migrate-create-react-app-to-vite/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the evolving landscape of web development, keeping up with efficient tools and processes is crucial for any developer looking to enhance performance and maintainability. Vite has emerged as a natural successor to Create React App (CRA) for many looking to build modern, single-page React applications. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk through the steps to migrate your project from CRA to Vite, with a focus on practicality and ease.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to fix “SyntaxError: Cannot use import statement outside a module”?</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-fix-syntaxerror-cannot-use-import-statement-outside-a-module/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-fix-syntaxerror-cannot-use-import-statement-outside-a-module/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In your development journey, encountering errors is a norm, but some can leave you scratching your head. One such instance is when you&amp;rsquo;re met with &amp;ldquo;Cannot use import statement outside a module&amp;rdquo; in JavaScript. This error can be a hurdle, but with the right guidance, you can overcome it easily. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the why and how of fixing this common issue, equipping you with the tools to continue coding without interruptions.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UI Component Libraries: Use or not to use [them] with epic fails and more...</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/ui-component-libraries-use-or-not-to-use-them-with-epic-fails-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/ui-component-libraries-use-or-not-to-use-them-with-epic-fails-and-more/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced world of web and mobile application development, time is of the essence. As such, developers are always looking for ways to speed up their development cycles while maintaining the quality of their applications. One way to do this is by using UI component libraries.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A UI component library is a collection of pre-built user interface elements that can be easily integrated into your application.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vue.js Forge 3</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/vue-js-forge-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/vue-js-forge-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As developers, we are constantly in search of new and exciting challenges to put our skills into practice. If you’ve been waiting for a challenge like that, then we’ve got some exciting news for you!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to use Bootstrap 5 in React.js - an original tutorial with (not original) examples</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/bootstrap-react-tutorial-with-examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/bootstrap-react-tutorial-with-examples/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bootstrap is a holy Grail for most of us - it&amp;rsquo;s the most popular HTML, CSS and most of all JS library in the world. And as a Christmas miracle—Bootstrap v5.3.0-alpha1 has arrived during the holiday break, so&amp;hellip; let&amp;rsquo;s dig inside and check how to use bootstrap in React.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top React UI Component Libraries in 2023</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/react-ui-component-libraries/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/react-ui-component-libraries/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Developers are consistently looking for the best tools for their projects. Numerous front-end developers agree that using a popular framework will keep the code simple and strong. This is why numerous programmers are now using the React UI Framework - a top-notch framework that offers excellent runtime performance for modern UIs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This makes it an ideal option for constructing components that are of the highest quality, can be used multiple times and are able to handle large numbers of requests and renderings.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;React allows you to create user interfaces that adjust to different platforms and browsers because it divides its data layer from the presentation logic. The React UI framework and component libraries are essential to JavaScript and make it possible to create customized user experiences.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article is about the most beneficial React Component Libraries available in 2023, so let&amp;rsquo;s dive in.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who’s NEXT?</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/whos-next/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/whos-next/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://coreui.io/product/next-js-dashboard-template/?theme=default-v3&#34;&gt;CoreUI PRO Next.js Admin Template&lt;/a&gt; coming in 3… 2… 1…&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why NEXT? Does it really give you the best developer experience with all the features you need for production: hybrid static &amp;amp; server rendering, TypeScript support, smart bundling, route pre-fetching, and more? And no config needed? Too good to be true ;)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Friday aka Black Week aka Bull Shit?</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/black-friday-aka-black-week-aka-bull-shit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/black-friday-aka-black-week-aka-bull-shit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Anyone else here think the whole black Friday thing is some Yankee Doodle bullshit? ;) you probably remember when few years ago 30,000 people bought crap on Black Friday… literally.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>React? We’ve got (no) problem. Top5 React issues.</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/react-weve-got-no-problem-top5-react-issues/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/react-weve-got-no-problem-top5-react-issues/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Commonly known as the most popular JavaScript framework… Wait… React JS is indeed based on JavaScript, but we’re not so sure about naming it a framework because… it’s rather a library? Which comes first, the chicken or the egg? ;) No matter if we prefer chicken or egg, there’s no argue that React.js is number 1. Netflix, Instagram, and Facebook are just at the beginning of the long list of web apps developed thanks to React.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI &amp; Vue.js Forge… cause 1 is just not enough!</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/coreui-vue-js-forge-cause-1-is-just-not-enough/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/coreui-vue-js-forge-cause-1-is-just-not-enough/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you were thinking on new and exciting ways to learn Vue and get that hands-on Vue.js experience – there’s another great chance to join the biggest Vue.js community.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vue.js Forge</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/vuejs-forge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/vuejs-forge/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you were thinking on new and exciting ways to learn Vue and get that hands-on Vue.js experience - here’s what you need to know!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to create a single page application using React.js</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-create-a-single-page-application-using-reactjs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-create-a-single-page-application-using-reactjs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this tutorial, you will learn how to create a single page application using ReactJS. You will learn how to create a simple ReactJS application that renders a simple message box.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>React v18.0 – finally is of legal age?</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/react-18-finally-is-of-legal-age/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/react-18-finally-is-of-legal-age/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s almost a month after official presentation on npm, so it’s we’re ready to roll with our remarks on the latest React version. As you know, CoreUI &lt;a href=&#34;https://coreui.io/&#34;&gt;Admin Panel&lt;/a&gt; is not another blend of 3rd parties’ free components and libraries. It&amp;rsquo;s the only Open-Source &lt;a href=&#34;https://coreui.io/react&#34;&gt;React Admin Dashboard Template&lt;/a&gt; built on the enterprise-grade hand-crafted &lt;a href=&#34;https://coreui.io/react/&#34;&gt;React UI Components Library&lt;/a&gt;. That’s why we’ve waited patiently for React v18.0, to materialize it e.g. here &lt;a href=&#34;https://coreui.io/react/&#34;&gt;https://coreui.io/react/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quo Vadis Vue.js</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/2022/01/17/quo-vadis-vue.js/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/2022/01/17/quo-vadis-vue.js/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You’ve probably seen CoreUI’s &lt;a href=&#34;https://coreui.io/vue/&#34;&gt;Vue Admin Dashboard Template &amp;amp; UI Components Library&lt;/a&gt;. If not, apart our hearts are broken, here’s a link: &lt;a href=&#34;https://coreui.io/vue/&#34;&gt;https://coreui.io/vue/&lt;/a&gt; ;)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We can see, that many of you’re asking about Vue.js tools designed by CoreUI. You like our “keep it simple” approach and Vue.js 3 full compatibility, which fuels our work.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10&#43; Free Bootstrap Admin Templates for your Web App 2022</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/free-bootstrap-admin-dashboard-templates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/free-bootstrap-admin-dashboard-templates/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The creation of professional dashboards is no problem. Thanks to this selection of free bootstrap templates, you will find a practical UI toolkit for your project. Each tool also includes a template for your dashboard that can be customizable to your project. When building the customized dashboard, you have the choice between the different elements and components offered in the template pack. Chart graphics, button alerts, or tables are just a few features you can add.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vue UI component libraries 2022</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/vue-ui-component-libraries/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/vue-ui-component-libraries/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Saying that Vue.js is one of the fastest-growing JavaScript frameworks is almost like saying nothing. It has a profound collection of external libraries and frameworks that make developing applications quick and easy, even without any prior experience. When talking about Vue’s growth, it relates to the framework’s simplicity, availability of libraries, components, and learning materials like e.g. vueschool.io to strengthen the ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple Black Friday</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/2021/11/26/simple-black-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/2021/11/26/simple-black-friday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Not long ago, a guy, let’s name him “Kyle” asked us about CoreUI’s Tips for developers to create stunning web or app. Anwer was easy: “keep it simple” :)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do we need UI components?</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/2021/10/27/do-we-need-ui-components/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/2021/10/27/do-we-need-ui-components/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s not a secret (especially here), that the User Interface (UI) is a huge part of every app. Some say that if the icon is the front door, the UI is the interior design [that’s why CoreUI brings you both icons and components ;)]. Of course, you can take the route of completely designing your own UI from scratch, but… we all suffer from a lack of time. So if you want to get it up and running fast while still having a polished finish, an appropriate UI library seems to be the right option.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can’t wait for what the future of Vue holds!</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/cant-wait-for-what-the-future-of-vue-holds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/cant-wait-for-what-the-future-of-vue-holds/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It cannot be an accident, cause just as we’ve released 90+ Bootstrap based&#xA;Vue.js components and directives our friends from VueSchool.io told us&#xA;about their Nuxt Nation Conference 2021. So, joint forces of CoreUI and&#xA;VueSchool are happy to announce, that a lot of good things will be brought&#xA;into Vue.js’ World this September.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI Vue.js components helped to win a Eurostat hackathon</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/coreui-vue-js-components-helped-to-win-a-eurostat-hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/coreui-vue-js-components-helped-to-win-a-eurostat-hackathon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Just a few weeks ago, a nice gentleman from Italy sent us a message:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Dear CoreUI, I am a researcher working at ISTAT, last week I participated in European Big Data Hackathon 2021, organized by Eurostat. And we won using CoreUI Vue.js!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sounds interesting? That’s just the beginning — let’s dig deeper, cause it’s getting hot in here…&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UI Components For Bootstrap — Part 1 by Mehwash Patel</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/2021/01/03/ui-components-for-bootstrap-part-1-by-mehwash-patel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/2021/01/03/ui-components-for-bootstrap-part-1-by-mehwash-patel/</guid>
      <description>CoreUI is a complete Dashboard UI Kit that allows you to quickly build UX friendly, responsive applications.&#xA;I’ll be writing about various Bootstrap components in detail in this series. Comment below if you’ve any questions or if you’d want me to write about a specific CoreUI component.&#xA;In Part 1 of this series, we’ll look at the components: Alert, Badge and Toast.&#xA;So without further ado, let’s get started.&#xA;Alert component is used to display message to the user.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 React Admin Templates &amp; Tools of the Year 2020</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/2020/12/21/top-10-react-admin-templates-tools-of-the-year-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/2020/12/21/top-10-react-admin-templates-tools-of-the-year-2020/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;2020 is almost over… Thanks to the pandemic, I believe that 99,9% of the global population will be celebrating this coming 2021. But before we&amp;rsquo;ll do so, enjoy your seat and take a look at this collection of the most beautiful and most all – reliable React Admin Templates.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earn Real Money on every sale you refer - become a CoreUI PRO affiliate today!</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/2020/08/20/earn-real-money-on-every-sale-you-refer-become-a-coreui-pro-affiliate-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/2020/08/20/earn-real-money-on-every-sale-you-refer-become-a-coreui-pro-affiliate-today/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- blank line --&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;embed-responsive embed-responsive-21by9&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;iframe class=&#34;embed-responsive-item&#34; src=&#34;https://coreui.io/images/blog/coreui-affiliate-program.mp4&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- blank line --&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$5000/month +&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It takes few minutes to join CoreUI’s Affiliate Program, just fill the simple online form. You can earn $5000/month and more by promoting our software on your website. But the best is yet to come…&#xA;In standard affiliate programs cookie has a 30-day life. Your referral needs to make a purchase within 30-days of clicking your affiliate link in order for you to get paid &amp;ndash; otherwise the lead will no longer be trackable. CoreUI’s Affiliate Program keeps track of your referral for 120 calendar days!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI Vue Laravel Admin Template – more than simple integration...</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/2020/07/20/coreui-vue-laravel-admin-template-more-than-simple-integration.../</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/2020/07/20/coreui-vue-laravel-admin-template-more-than-simple-integration.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bootstrap Admin Template with Laravel. Really? Sure do cause apart from the integration our team enhanced the template with the examples of useful features implementations.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bootstrap v5 arrived – even though it’s alpha, we’re eager to get more</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/2020/06/17/bootstrap-v5-arrived-even-though-its-alpha-were-eager-to-get-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/2020/06/17/bootstrap-v5-arrived-even-though-its-alpha-were-eager-to-get-more/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We bet you all know the Buggles’ song:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9 mb-3&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;iframe class=&#34;embed-responsive-item&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/W8r-tXRLazs&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Almost every week last years we’ve heard that jQuery is slowly going into nowhere, when e.g. Vue.js is striving it’s way to popularity. So is the story with the Buggles’ song “Video killed the radio star”, where title seems to tell everything. Latest Bootstrap Blog: &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.getbootstrap.com/2020/06/16/bootstrap-5-alpha/&#34;&gt;https://blog.getbootstrap.com/2020/06/16/bootstrap-5-alpha/&lt;/a&gt; seems to be the final conformation for Jquery – bolded text tells everything: “Bootstrap no longer depends on jQuery”.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And you know what? CoreUI did the same almost year ago. It’s good to know that we’re in a good company – what’s even more sexy is that we did it first 😊&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI 3.0 hooks on React.js?</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/2020/05/31/coreui-3.0-hooks-on-react.js/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/2020/05/31/coreui-3.0-hooks-on-react.js/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You know CoreUI React.js for so many years, e.g. thanks to Free and Pro versions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now it&amp;rsquo;s time for V3… What&amp;rsquo;s the difference?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Reactstrap has been replaced with our own code, which with the new context API and one naming convention across all components – brings a lot of new features that help to create amazing user interfaces. Eager to know more? Take a look…&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI #stayHome #getPro for Free</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/2020/04/30/coreui-stayhome-getpro-for-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/2020/04/30/coreui-stayhome-getpro-for-free/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;No matter if it’s Poland, the USA, Span, Italy, Russia, or India – we allface the same problem. There’s no wonder then, that many times you’ve been asking us if we could support the worldwide struggle with the COVID-19 spreading. The answer was always easy: YES, YES, YES. That’s why we give you an -25% discount with #stayHomecode and if it’s not enough&amp;hellip; you can get the PRO license completelyfor free.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy Easter &amp; #stayhome?</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/2020/04/10/happy-easter-stayhome/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 14:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/2020/04/10/happy-easter-stayhome/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This supposes to be a completely different newsletter… Our team wanted to wish you a pleasant Easter and enjoy your free time. But things have changed drastically and most of us change our scope. Really? Of course, some things could’ve been done better, yet it is hard to blame anyone for what has or has not been done, this situation is difficult as it is, the main effort now should go towards winning this uneven battle…&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI Vue.js components library– gimme more?</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/2020/03/06/coreui-vue.js-components-library-gimme-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 14:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/2020/03/06/coreui-vue.js-components-library-gimme-more/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Switching to another &lt;a href=&#34;https://coreui.io/vue/&#34;&gt;Vue components library&lt;/a&gt; is never easy. There are multitudes of them available on the market and we all know that you can&amp;rsquo;t teach an old dog new tricks. So you may ask why should I try CoreUI Vue.js? Below you’ll get 5 good (not bad) reasons.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreUI 3k&#43; icons set – why the … did we do this?!</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/2020/01/02/coreui-3k-icons-set-why-the-did-we-do-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/2020/01/02/coreui-3k-icons-set-why-the-did-we-do-this/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Webpage or an app interface means nothing if it’s not glued with sexy set of icons. You know it best. So to be honest, we’ve got an answer for above question. But… there’s always a “but” 😉 You may ask why we let more than 3000 icons to be downloaded for free? X-mas gift, Black Friday in December, New Year’s madness? No way – from now on, you can use CoreUI icons for free. We’re open source, so it should be for free. Save your time and drag them in your design.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laravel rockz?</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/2019/12/05/laravel-rockz/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/2019/12/05/laravel-rockz/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You’ve been asking us to introduce CoreUI for #Laravel and as you know – &lt;strong&gt;your wish is our command&lt;/strong&gt; 😉, so here it is: &lt;a href=&#34;https://coreui.io/laravel/&#34;&gt;https://coreui.io/laravel/&lt;/a&gt; You can check both Free and PRO versions. What’s inside? Saying a bunch of responsive, customizable, and reusable components you need to create modern, beautiful, responsive apps is saying (almost) nothing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are you ready for CoreUI 3.0?</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/2019/11/06/are-you-ready-for-coreui-3.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/2019/11/06/are-you-ready-for-coreui-3.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-beta-version-has-just-been-released&#34;&gt;The beta version has just been released.&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some say… 😉 that CoreUI admin template is one of the most popular open-source &lt;a href=&#34;https://coreui.io&#34;&gt;admin panel template&lt;/a&gt;. Some may ask – why? Because it delivers all responsive, customizable, and reusable components, you might need to create simply beautiful &amp;amp; responsive apps. But the beauty would be nothing without time-to-market. So please cordially welcome CoreUI 3.0 (beta).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leave well alone?</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/2019/09/30/leave-well-alone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/2019/09/30/leave-well-alone/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We believe that we all know that sentence, but to be honest - like humans, companies change over time and, when it does, a brand redesign becomes necessary. We bet you noticed latest changes in our design and if you’re interested in more detailed information, pls read this post.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s new and updated in CoreUI 3</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/2019/07/01/whats-new-and-updated-in-coreui-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/2019/07/01/whats-new-and-updated-in-coreui-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Version 3 has been re-written and re-designed completely from scratch. Here are the key changes in v3:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bootstrap Icons</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/2018/03/20/bootstrap-icons/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/2018/03/20/bootstrap-icons/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bootstrap 4 doesn’t include an icon library by default, that&amp;rsquo;s why many developers looking for best icons. Where you can find awesome Bootstrap Icons for your project?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migration from Bootstrap 3 to Bootstrap 4</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/2018/01/31/migration-from-bootstrap-3-to-bootstrap-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 10:29:11 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/2018/01/31/migration-from-bootstrap-3-to-bootstrap-4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bootstrap 4 is a major rewrite of the entire project. The most notable changes are summarized below, followed by more specific changes to relevant components.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to upgrade Bootstrap 4 alpha 6 to Bootstrap 4 beta</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/2017/08/12/how-to-upgrade-bootstrap-4-alpha-6-to-bootstrap-4-beta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 18:29:11 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/2017/08/12/how-to-upgrade-bootstrap-4-alpha-6-to-bootstrap-4-beta/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After two years in the making, Bootstrap creators finally released first beta of Bootstrap 4. In latest version of Bootstrap 4 more then 650 files was changed, 67k lines was added, and 82k lines was deleted.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to migrate from Bootstrap 3 to Bootstrap 4 Beta</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/2017/07/10/how-to-migrate-from-bootstrap-3-to-bootstrap-4-beta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 18:29:11 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/2017/07/10/how-to-migrate-from-bootstrap-3-to-bootstrap-4-beta/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bootstrap 4 is a major rewrite of the entire project. The most notable changes are summarized below, followed by more specific changes to relevant components.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s new in Bootstrap 4 ?</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/2017/07/04/whats-new-in-bootstrap-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 18:29:11 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/2017/07/04/whats-new-in-bootstrap-4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bootstrap 4 is just round the corner. Bootstrap 4 is a major rewrite of the entire project. Here is list of major changes in latest version of Bootstrap.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bootstrap 3.0.2 and 3.0.1 - right direction?</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/2013/11/08/bootstrap-3.0.2-and-3.0.1-right-direction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/2013/11/08/bootstrap-3.0.2-and-3.0.1-right-direction/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There’s no discussion that, Bootstrap is one of the most popular responsive frameworks available, since Twitter released it in 2011. Thanks to an extensive library of cutting edge components, add-ons and plugins it enables fresh ideas and unconventional approach to every next web project. So there’s no wonder then, that not more than a week ago we’ve heard about Bootstrap 3.0.1, and just two days ago we’ve got Bootstrap 3.0.2. But as our dear old grannies used to say: never too much of a good thing…&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bootstrap – unlimited responsive template?</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/2013/08/24/bootstrap-unlimited-responsive-template/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2013 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/2013/08/24/bootstrap-unlimited-responsive-template/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Show me your cards (not, not Bootstrap themes yet)… As we’re all waiting for top mobile devices premieres, I bet we’re all satisfied right now. Apple showed its iPhone 5c and iPhone 5s – for the first time in history mobile device has been equipped with 64 bit CPU – future yet to come? On the other side, Samsung launched its Gear and Note III during IFA fair trade in Berlin&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genius Bootstrap Admin Template</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/2013/08/24/genius-bootstrap-admin-template/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2013 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/2013/08/24/genius-bootstrap-admin-template/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We introduced our Genius &lt;a href=&#34;https://coreui.io&#34;&gt;Bootstrap Admin Template&lt;/a&gt;. But does the name oblige? If we look at some of the features like Bootstrap 3.0.0, write with LESS and almost 1500 icon (among them Glyphicons PRO), you can easily say that Genius Bootstrap can be(come) Einstein in the world of Bootstrap templates.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
