<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>javascript on CoreUI</title>
    <link>https://coreui.io/tags/javascript/</link>
    <description>Recent content in javascript on CoreUI</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 01:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://coreui.io/tags/javascript/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to round a number to two decimal places in JavaScript</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-round-a-number-to-two-decimal-places-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-round-a-number-to-two-decimal-places-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the ever-evolving landscape of web development, mastering JavaScript nuances can significantly enhance your applications&amp;rsquo; functionality and user experience. A joint yet critical operation in numerous computing scenarios is to round numbers to a specific number of decimal places. Among these, rounding to two decimal places is particularly relevant across financial calculations, statistical reporting, and data presentation for its balance between precision and readability. This comprehensive guide will walk you through the intricacies of rounding numbers to two decimal places in JavaScript, ensuring you confidently apply this operation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to check if a string is a number in JavaScript</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-check-if-string-is-number-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-check-if-string-is-number-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the realm of web development, the versatility and power of JavaScript stand unchallenged. It is pivotal in adding interactivity to websites, working with data, and creating complex web applications. A common hurdle developers often stumble upon is determining whether a given piece of text—more formally, a string—represents a number. This validation is crucial for data processing, form submissions, and other scenarios where numeric input is expected. This comprehensive article explores the methods and best practices for checking if a string is a number in JavaScript, ensuring your code is robust, reliable, and ready for real-world usage.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to check if an array is empty in JavaScript?</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-check-if-an-array-is-empty-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-check-if-an-array-is-empty-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the ever-evolving world of web development, JavaScript stands as a cornerstone, powering dynamic and interactive elements across countless websites and applications. Among its many tasks, one seemingly straightforward yet pivotal operation is determining whether an array is empty. This operation is crucial in various scenarios, such as enabling or disabling buttons based on user input or ensuring data integrity before processing. In this article, part of the &amp;ldquo;how to&amp;rdquo; series, we delve into the intricacies of checking for empty arrays in JavaScript. This guide promises to enlighten those new to the programming world and provide valuable insights for seasoned developers.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering JavaScript List Comprehension: The Ultimate Guide</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/javascript-list-comprehension/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/javascript-list-comprehension/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;JavaScript list comprehension may not have a dedicated syntax like Python or Perl, but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean it&amp;rsquo;s any less powerful. In a realm dominated by dynamic data and the need for efficient operations on arrays, understanding how to perform list comprehension in JavaScript is indispensable for developers. This comprehensive guide will walk you through the practical nuances of array manipulation using JavaScript, offering vivid examples to transform you into a master of efficient list handling.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Inline Styles in React.js: Enhancing Your Components with Style</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-use-inline-styles-in-react/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-use-inline-styles-in-react/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Are you looking to refine your React.js components with a dash of styling, but find yourself tangled in a web of CSS files? Fear not! Inline styles in React can be a powerful tool for developers to directly insert styling properties into their components. Here, we delve into the art of using react inline style, answering critical questions and unveiling the best practices to maximize the potential of your React.js applications. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re painting your first component or tweaking an existing masterpiece, this guide will illuminate the path to impeccable styling within your React projects.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding and Resolving the “Objects Are Not Valid as a React Child” Error in React Development</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-fix-objects-are-not-valid-as-a-react-child/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-fix-objects-are-not-valid-as-a-react-child/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;React has revolutionized the way developers build user interfaces, standing out for its modular approach through components and state management. As with any robust technology, developers, from beginners to veterans, encounter their share of error messages. One that often crops up is the &lt;code&gt;Objects Are Not Valid as a React Child&lt;/code&gt; error. In this comprehensive article, we&amp;rsquo;ll dissect the causes of this error and provide actionable solutions for overcoming it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to get the last element in an array in JavaScript</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-get-the-last-element-in-an-array-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-get-the-last-element-in-an-array-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;JavaScript arrays are fundamental structures in any developer&amp;rsquo;s arsenal, designed to store multiple values in a single, easy-to-manage variable. But no matter how proficient you are in JavaScript, there are always new tricks to learn and old ones to be reminded of. One such handy trick is retrieving the last element of an array—an operation that might seem straightforward but comes with nuances worth understanding. In this deep dive into JavaScript arrays, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore multiple ways to get to that elusive last item and offer insights into which method suits your coding needs best.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to compare dates with JavaScript</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-compare-dates-with-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-compare-dates-with-javascript/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As the digital world intertwines more deeply with our lives, understanding the intricacies of web development becomes increasingly relevant. JavaScript stands at the forefront of this realm, with its ability to enrich user experiences. Among its many capabilities, the power to compare dates in JavaScript is a particularly useful skill that enables developers to deal with schedules, events, and time-based data more effectively.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to disable a button in JavaScript</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-disable-a-button-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-disable-a-button-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the intricate dance of web development, JavaScript plays a crucial role in choreographing dynamic interactions. One such interaction is the ability to enable or disable buttons on a web page. Disabling a button may seem straightforward, but it serves as a critical user experience (UX) feature, ensuring users only take actions when the time is right. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the art of disabling a button in JavaScript, guiding you through a variety of methods with intuitive code examples—and don&amp;rsquo;t worry; we&amp;rsquo;ll keep the jargon in check.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to check if a key exists in JavaScript object?</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-check-if-a-key-exists-in-javascript-object/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-check-if-a-key-exists-in-javascript-object/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the intricate world of JavaScript, a common task for developers is determining whether a specific key exists within an object. It&amp;rsquo;s an elementary, yet crucial skill that can significantly affect the flow and reliability of your code. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll unearth the various methods to perform this check, unravel their nuances, and understand how to apply them, even in complex nested structures. By the end of this article, you&amp;rsquo;ll be equipped with the expertise to write robust and error-free JavaScript applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to remove elements from a JavaScript Array</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-remove-element-from-javascript-array/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-remove-element-from-javascript-array/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Have you ever faced the challenge of removing a specific item from an array in JavaScript and found yourself puzzled with various methods and unsure which one to use? Arrays are fundamental structures in programming that store collections of data. However, understanding how to manipulate them efficiently, especially when it comes to removing elements, is crucial for a streamlined code. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;re going to demystify the process of removing elements from JavaScript arrays. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a budding programmer or a seasoned developer looking to brush up on your skills, this guide is designed to provide you with everything you need to handle array modifications with confidence.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Migrate from create-react-app to Vite?</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-migrate-create-react-app-to-vite/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-migrate-create-react-app-to-vite/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the evolving landscape of web development, keeping up with efficient tools and processes is crucial for any developer looking to enhance performance and maintainability. Vite has emerged as a natural successor to Create React App (CRA) for many looking to build modern, single-page React applications. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk through the steps to migrate your project from CRA to Vite, with a focus on practicality and ease.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to fix “SyntaxError: Cannot use import statement outside a module”?</title>
      <link>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-fix-syntaxerror-cannot-use-import-statement-outside-a-module/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://coreui.io/blog/how-to-fix-syntaxerror-cannot-use-import-statement-outside-a-module/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In your development journey, encountering errors is a norm, but some can leave you scratching your head. One such instance is when you&amp;rsquo;re met with &amp;ldquo;Cannot use import statement outside a module&amp;rdquo; in JavaScript. This error can be a hurdle, but with the right guidance, you can overcome it easily. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the why and how of fixing this common issue, equipping you with the tools to continue coding without interruptions.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
